A Guide to the Libertarian Party Papers, 1972-1984
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Libertarian Party Papers 1972-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
10187-s
This collection contains ca. 290 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This material was made a gift to the Library on July 31, 1984, by Roger Lea MacBride of Charlottesville, Virginia.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of ca. 290 items, 1972-1984, concerning the Libertarian Party. Correspondents include Edward E. Clark and John E. Erb (Folder: "Correspondence of Honey S. Lanham"), Norma Lee Browning (Folder: "Correspondence of Roger Lea MacBride"), and David F. Nolan, Tom Westgard, and Paul Grant (Folder: "Correspondence of the Libertarian Party"). Also included are campaign literature concerning Dave Bergland's 1984 candidacy for the presidency as well as for other political races, material of the Libertarian National Committee, miscellaneous papers, news releases, printed material, and three campaign buttons.
Contents List
- Correspondence
  - Correspondence of Honey S. Lanham 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence of Roger Lea MacBride 1975-1984 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence of the Libertarian Party 1981-1984 (Box 1)
- Material re: the Libertarian Party
  - Articles re the Libertarian Party by Roger Lea MacBride 1975 (Box 1)
  - Campaign Literature 1972-1984, n.d., 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Campaign Literature: Dave Bergland for President 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - Libertarian National Committee 1975-1984 (Box 1)
  - Libertarian Party Literature 1972-1974, n.d. (Box 2)
  - News Releases of the Libertarian Party 1974-1983 (Box 2)
  - Printed Material re the Libertarian Party 1973-1984 (Box 2)